I'm here in my perfect imperfection to
make today's video and I don't even know
what it's gonna be about hit record and
I don't have a topic in mind but I
really want to create this together and
that's where I am today I'm just I'm not
done doing it by myself I'm gonna
continue moving forward and do whatever
I need to do to see this come into the
world but I really want people to work
on it with I want to video chat with
people and because I don't think I'm
gonna find the people I mean I could
find the people in Vancouver but the
right people are probably all over the
world and I want a board of directors
people who are passionate about creating
a better world a world where nobody has
to live in poverty and where we create
the tools together for people to be able
to collaborate so that when we do have
an idea it's so much easier to get it
out into the world because the world
needs solutions and love in connection
right now so much and I need those
things so much I want love and
connection and community and I have it
in a lot of ways and I'm so grateful for
the ways that I do have it but I want to
create this together it's not supposed
to be created by one person it's not
supposed to be a CEO malted like a
corporation that's what's been done and
it's being done and it can offer some
solutions but this solution is only done
through a group of people inspiring
other people to join and as we slowly
start the ball rolling and people are
inspired by not only hopefully the
amazing lives we're living but also the
technology that we're creating and see
how it all can work together and improve
our lives personally and up to the
global level and I am feel like I just
have heaviness on my heart still from
yesterday where I don't know I don't
know how to get this out there I
I'm not a great video put her together I
don't look very well even though it's my
only language I am NOT the best at
communicating my ideas but I am amazing
at coming up with the ideas I for some
reason this idea came through me and I
understand that I'm the person who had
supposed to have come through because
only only I can do this only I can put
this idea into the world and that I'm
supposed to be struggling with it
because as I find a way to put it out
there it's part of the solution for
everyone to put their ideas out there as
I create a it's not my first project but
a dating site a dating app that works
for the rest of us who hate online and
hey I maybe aren't the most aren't the
greatest at getting in relationships but
I'm amazing once we're in them creating
that together with everyone's that we
can't community like that's what I'm
gonna get someone and I'm not not open
to it until then I mean I'm going to be
as open as I can be but the things that
I struggle with in my life and the
solutions that I could create through
technology to solve those for myself
solve them for everybody else too and I
know I'm not the best at flirting and
going on dates and showing o me the good
pieces of myself I just I don't play
games and I only show all of me and I
don't know how to do it any other way
and that's okay
that's exactly who I'm supposed to be
you know attract the right people at the
right time for both my personal life and
as well as my passion my project and
this is sit with that and be okay with
it that the right people and but I'm so
anxious all the time of this timeline
this in my fist my phone goes up this
timeline that our planet needs solutions
and it's something less anxious about my
personal life like the right person
comes along at the right time and yes
I'm getting older but I don't think
that's a need to solve that in the world
too because age brings wisdom and beauty
it doesn't buttes
why wouldn't you yeah I don't know can
still you still can have meaningful love
and let and life left your 9400 so being
37 it's not gonna stop me and I already
created the love of my life and my
daughter so I have an amazing life I
love it
but the pieces that I want to improve or
what I want to improve for everybody so
today's video I don't even know what the
title is gonna be I'll have to rewatch
it and come up with the title but for
those of you who may be watching in the
future thanks for watching